http://www.knox.nsw.edu.au/about/public-information/annual-report-and-policies

Annual Report and PoliciesKEY POLICIES AND DOCUMENTSEnrolment Application Form and Conditions of EnrolmentConditions of EnrolmentOverseas Student - Enrolment Application FormPrivacy PolicyStandard Collection NoticeKnox Child Protection PolicyProcedures for Handling Allegations of Staff Misconduct and Reportable ConductComplaints Handling PolicyKnox Report Service for Raising Matters of Serious Concern PolicyAnti-Bullying PolicyParent Communications PolicySports Camps and Skills Clinics Cancellation PolicyVolunteer Code of ConductTerms of Use - Knox Social MediaAnnual Report for NSW Education Standards AuthorityKnox Grammar School Strategic Direction 2018-2022Overseas Student Enrolment PolicyKSAA Safe Training Protocols - Home Workouts Online 2020PRICING POLICYKnox Grammar School, Old Knox Grammarians and Knox Parents' Association sets its fees and charges at a competitive level when measured against other similar schools. All of our prices are in Australian dollars (AUD) and include GST (Goods and Services Tax) where applicable.REFUND POLICYPayments made to Knox Grammar School, Old Knox Grammarians and Knox Parents' Association are not refundable unless this is specifically indicated in relation to a particular activity. A complete copy of the School's Conditions of Enrolment is available on this page.PRIVACY POLICYKnox Grammar School, Old Knox Grammarians and Knox Parents' Association are committed to privacy. For more information, please read our Privacy Policy.View our Privacy PolicyFurther ReadingSuggestionsCommunications and Publications: Read our publications, including The Thistle and Headmaster's Report.QUICKLINKS... select a page Knox PrepWahroonga PrepSenior SchoolAquatic CentreOnline PaymentsBook a School TourRequest a ProspectusSport FixturesContact us and LocationSEARCH:PreviousTerm DatesNext History of KnoxKNOX GRAMMAR SCHOOL2 Borambil Street,
Wahroonga NSW 2076,
AUSTRALIAContact UsPrivacy Policy Facebook Twitter Instagram VimeoSubscribe to our eNewsletterSIGN UPABN 43709615471
CRICOS Provider
Code: 00399EDesign Credit
